wantickets.com 2015-07-11

# Wantickets United States - United States Wantickets Events

PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THE Wantickets RDM, LLC. WEBSITE (the "Site"). 

:: OUR PRIVACY POLICY 

We are committed to protecting our user’s privacy. To that end, we offer this statement to inform our users of how we define, gather and utilize personal information. We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify or otherwise alter this policy at any time. Such changes and/or modifications shall become effective immediately upon the posting thereof. Without limiting the foregoing, we may occasionally notify you by email about changes to the Site or provide notices of changes by displaying notices or links to notices to you generally on the Site. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes and/or modifications will constitute your acceptance of the revised privacy policy. For your information, this page was last updated on Tuesday, March 31, 2015. 

In an effort to provide more comprehensive services to our users, affiliates and advertising partners, our site may now be gathering interest based information and using one or more of the following interest-based advertising collection activities: 

  * Remarketing
  * Interest Categories
  * Similar audiences
  * Other types of interest-based advertising

This information will potentially be used by third-party vendors, including Google, to show our Display Ads across desktop web browsers, tablets and mobile devices.

Third-party vendors, including Google, may use cookies on our site to serve ads based upon your past usage of our website.

Any visitor to our site can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting Google’s [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjU0j00j9Lkx_9E3P_OYcLSwSxiCu6dSUG8Oso80g3DXaRX61eTJVieCWI-KO9Kd4-NII2cpwNpVvKFxV_Zlifxf6P8v2woposaXtwffLQZ5zQNwjpgZ-tT1uQ_GQBlmoIlt0G-R6WI5WmIvheCt-281upCaX1I7wdbtgdv5pfddfrDzfo). Alternatively, any visitor can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out ad-on page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

We define personal information as information that includes a person's full name, address, telephone number, date of birth and/or email address or any other information that is tied to individually identifiable information that would allow someone to identify or contact you, unless stated otherwise herein or on the Site. We can gather information on our users in two different ways: (1) cookie technology; and (2) voluntary submissions. 

We utilize cookie technology to collect data regarding the number of visits a person has made to our site. This data is stored in aggregate form and is in no way singled out in an individual file. This information allows us to know what pages/sites are of interest to our users and what pages/sites may be of less interest. Such information is utilized in revising the website to better meet our user’s needs and interests. 

We also collect personally identifiable information from users through voluntary submissions, said information may be provided to our Affiliates for future marketing efforts. We use good faith efforts to make it clear why the information is being collected and what it will be used for. In the event that this information is being shared with a third party affiliate, sponsor or advertiser, we will use good faith efforts to post a notice on the Site clearly stating that the information is being shared and/or give the user the opportunity to opt-in to authorize the sharing of such information. 

Unless specified otherwise on the Site, users must be 18 years or older before registering in any of our sweepstakes or contests. When sweepstakes or contests are open to users 13-17 years old, we will collect only first and last names, phone numbers and email addresses for prize fulfillment purposes only, unless otherwise stated on the Site. 

If a sweepstakes or contest winner is under 18 years old, we will require a consent form signed by the winner's parent or guardian in order to award the prize. We have taken steps to ensure that personally identifiable information collected is secure, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to its database servers, as well as electronic security systems and password protections which guard against unauthorized access. 

We encourage users to be smart about choosing when, and to whom to release information online. Additionally, we will allow users or their parents to opt out of the Wantickets RDM, LLC. database in the following manners: 

(1) To remove your name or your child's name from the database of an specific Wantickets RDM, LLC. sweepstakes or contest or other similar activity: Send an e-mail to [support@wantickets.com](mailto:support@wantickets.com) with the following information in the body of the e-mail form:

Name, Email address used to register, Name of Wantickets RDM, LLC. sweepstakes or contest or activity, entered Username (if applicable) 

(2) To remove your name or your child's name from the Wantickets RDM, LLC. database entirely including, but not limited to, registration for all of Wantickets websites:

Send an e-mail to [support@wantickets.com](mailto:support@wantickets.com) with the following information in the body of the e-mail form: Name, Email address used to register, Username (if applicable)
